# RAYMOND CHUNG

Archung95.github.io ≥ 12rc51@queensu.ca in raymondchung95 • Crchung95



# **SUMMARY:**

I am a developer from Toronto, ON with a love for programming, sports and people. I have entrepreneur experience working at a startup and from launching one myself. I am also involved in an initiative to empower female professionals through coding in the Kingston community.



# **EDUCATION**

## **Queen's University**

Kingston, ON, Canada Computer Science (Honours) Graduating May 2017

### **Queen's University**

Kingston, ON, Canada Education Expected Graduation May 2018



# **SKILLS**

### Languages:

Python / HTML, CSS / Java / PHP / JavaScript / Swift

### **Technologies:**

Bash / Git / Bootstrap / AngularJS / jQuery / Node.js + **Express** 

### Design:

Photoshop / Illustrator / Sketch 3

# **ACTIVITIES**

- IT Director of Queen's Startup Summit (2016-2017)
- Member of Software Developer's Club (2016-Present)
- Peer Tutor of a variety of Computer Science courses (2014-Present)

# **HACKATHONS**

- QHacks 2016
- Hack the North 2016

# **EXPERIENCE**

### Clarifai Champion (Remote Developer Evangelist), Clarifai Aug 2016 - Present

- Learning how to support the tech community locally and online by presenting at talks and workshops, mentoring at events, and contributing to open-source API

# Workshop & Curriculum Developer, Sudo Labs

June 2016 - Present

- Designed the web development and Python workshops and curriculums attended by 20+ people
- Organization featured in the Kingston Whig newspaper

# Web & iOS Developer, COMPSA Web Services

Web: July 2015 - Present, iOS: May 2016 - Present

- Develop and maintain websites and iPhone apps for studentrun clubs and organizations using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and Bootstrap for websites and Swift for apps.
- Design websites and mock-ups using Sketch 3

# **Teaching Assistant**. Queen's University

Jan 2016 - April 2016, Sept 2016 - Present

- Led CISC P81: Computers: Applications & Implications
- Proctored, assisted and graded over 90 tests and weekly lab assignments

# Research Assistant, Queen's University

May 2016 - Aug 2016

- Worked on debugging URML toolkit and implemented a functionality for a teaching toolkit
- Worked mainly in Java with Xtext & Xtend framework

# </> PORTFOLIO

# **Application Portal**, Web Application

- Created an application portal for the Queen's Startup Summit to make the application process more efficient and effective to handle over 100 applications by implementing statistical analysis
- Built using the MEAN stack (MongoDb, Express, AngularJs and Node.is)

### Walkhome, Mobile Application

- Personal safety app made for Walkhome, a student-run safety service at Queen's University
- Worked on the front-end side by creating the map and search functionality on the iOS version of the app